CURRICULUM VITAE

Full name: Bui Thi Van

Gender: Female

Date of Birth: 10-10-1993 Marital Status: Single

Address: 25T1 Hoang Dao Thuy, Trung Hoa Ward, Cau Giay District,

Ha Noi City.

Cell Phone: 0979 814 134 Email: van.bt.38@gmail.com

Website: https://vanbui93.github.io/my_cv/



INTRODUCTION

I have 3 years of working as Technical Support in Vietnam's e-commerce website and 5 years working as Front End Developer for offshore companies like Japan and Korea.

In the companies I have worked for, I have always been trusted and appreciated by my superiors for my dedication and hard work.

I'm also good at communication with everyone so if I have the opportunity to work at your company I believe that I'll be an excellent employee too.

I hope to have a chance to present in more detail if the company chooses to interview me.

EDUCATION

I graduated from **Ho Chi Minh City Industry And Trade College** (2011-2014) My major is **Computer Science** (2011-2014): Good

SKILLS

Programming languages:

- HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Liquid, SASS /SCSS.
- Strong knowledge in hand-coding HTML/CSS, converting from PSD, Figma, Zeplin,... to HTML/CSS, Javascript. Basic Knowledge of ReactJS (Next JS)
- Database: Firebase, PostgreSQL, MySQL Experience with GIT, Postman
- Can understand ES2015 (ES6).
- Order skills: Photoshop, Zeplin, Figma, Dreamweaver, VS Code
- Ability to learn new technology quickly
- Experience with website responsive, SEO Technical & mobile friendly

Client persuasion skills:

- I have experience as a technical support team lead at Haravan company and support customers to use Haravan's e-commerce platform and consult on choosing the right solution for the business model of each customer.
- Work as a freelance web developer: Meet customers directly to exchange quotes.
- Own business: call and chat with customers about self-sold products 2 self-employed websites:

www.phucngocan.com
https://vongdautambibac.blogspot.com

Problem-solving skills:

- As the team leader, I always have to hold the hotline to solve urgent problems that arise such as system errors, reassure customers and contact the technical department to solve the problem.

Languages:

- English TOEIC 580
- Japanese N3 JLPT

EXPERIENCE RECORD

From 02-2022 To Present: Hivelab VINA

- Position: Web developer

- Descriptions: Developing website UI for Korean clients.

- Typical projects: Kakao Games, Hyundai Oilbank

From 11-2020 To 11-2021: Cube System Viet Nam

Position: Web developer

- Descriptions:
 - Developing website UI for Japanese clients.
 - Support QA team to test manual in Japanese in free time
- Typical projects: Mizuho Bank

From 06-2017 To 09-2020: Transcosmos Viet Nam

- Position: Frontend Team Lead
- Descriptions:
 - Receive projects from Japanese manager and assign them to members.
 - Manage the team's work performance.
 - Manage the absence of team members and report back to the Japanese Manager.
 - Weekly report meetings on team performance, ways to improve performance and finding new projects.
 - Build checklists to avoid product failures.
 - Converting from PSD, Zeplin, Figma,... to pixel perfect using HTML/CSS and Javascript for Japanese clients.
- Typical projects: Suntory, Hoya glasses

Also, while I was working for this company, I was appointed to go on a business trip to the Head Quarter of the company in Tokyo, Japan for a period of three months

From 09-2014 To 06-2017: Haravan.com

- Position: Technical Support Team Lead
- Descriptions:
 - Responsible for building, and organizing work for the team.
 - Get feedback from clients and convey it to the producer
 - Training on the system and code (Liquid) for new members.
 - Weekly report meetings on the team's activities, Directly recommended to the Director about policies and the payroll sheet for the team.
 - Build content for the "user guide" page of the e-commerce website system.

I also support many big Vietnamese clients such as Vinamilk, the Face shop, Juno, The Coffee House, Aeon Eshop, iBasic, Aothun.vn... Also I had experience working with partners such as giaohangnhanh, viettel post, giaohangtietkiem, kiotviet, Suno...

CERTIFICATES, AWARDS

2013: Ho Chi Minh City Industry and Trade College Prize

2015 - Haravan Company: The Employee Excellence Award

2017 - Haravan Company: Dedication Award

2018 - Transcosmos Company: Business improvement Award

2018 - Transcosmos Company: Revenue Development Award

CAREER EXPECTATION

What is my career objective?

Try to learn as much as possible and do my best to accomplish my task I want to improve my skills according to the company's development Fluent my English to serve my work

INTERESTED

Listening to music, reading newspapers, traveling, watching films, cooking, growing flower Enjoy yoga, camping, picnic,...